IMAN MALIKI

+6283160993225 | 11imanmaliki@gmail.com | linkedin.com/imanmaliki | https://iman.menggenggam.asia

Bojong, Pandeglang Banten, 42274

Hello, I'm Iman Maliki, a software developer with 2+ years of experience, I can work as a backend for making APIs and also as a frontend for web applications. I want to grow up together with your company and give all of my experience and dedication for achieve company goals.

Work Experiences

PT DIDANATANECA TEKNOLOGI INDONESIA - Jakarta,

Nov 2022 - Present

Indonesia

Software/Platform Developer

- Build DSOP project for managing WiFi Routers and 500+ Users connect with Radiusdesk. My role is as full stack developer and the task is for creating views and also backend for application using Laravel as a main framework, MySQL, PHP, PPOB API, JWT, Linux Server and others.
- Build a DNE Track project with IoT for tracking device location and some other custom able data to server from IoT device using
 Astrocast satellite and Arduino Uno. My role is as full stack who build both IoT code using Arduino IDE and website using Laravel also
 integrate with Astrocast.

PT Lumos Inisiatif Indonesia - Jakarta Selatan, Indonesia

Oct 2021 - Oct 2022

Software Developer

- Project Internal App for employees of PT Lumos Inisiatif Indonesia, is responsible for continuing the creation of the website, especially
 in the display section to match the existing design. The technologies used are: Laravel, Bootstrap, PostgreSQL, JQuery. PHP and
 JavaScript Programming Languages.
- Project Bakoel Omah is a website for buying and selling F&B products. Responsible for creating the appearance and functionality of the application as well as integration with social media Instagram (Instagram Graph API). The technologies used are Laravel, Instagram Graph API, Selenium, NodeJS, Bootstrap, PostgreSQL, JQuery. PHP, JavaScript and Python.
- Project Skilledin is a website for organizing tasks based on Key Results and Objectives so company can see the performance of a
 particular person or team, in this project my role is as a Front End Developer. The technologies used are ReactJs, NodeJs, NPM, and
 Axios.

Sewasi - Bandar Lampung, Indonesia

Aug 2020 - Mar 2021

Frontend Developer (Part-time)

• The project is an application for renting sports fields for users, the role in this project is as a Front End Developer. The technologies used are ReactJS, NodeJS, NPM, and Axios.

Education Level

SMA Negeri 1 Pandeglang - Pandeglang, Indonesia

Jul 2014 - May 2017

Senior High School in Natural Science (IPA)

Institut Teknologi Sumatera - Lampung Selatan, Indonesia

Aug 2017 - Sep 2021

Bachelor Degree in Informatics Engineering, 3.25/4.00

Organisational Experience

Complexity - Lampung Selatan, Indonesia

Feb 2018 - Dec 2020

Member

· Learn about competitive programming contest with all members

Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Website: https://iman.menggenggam.asia
- Achievements: Finalist Gemastik 12, Finalist Gemastik 13, dan Finalist Hology 3.0
- Soft Skills: PHP, Laravel, PostgreSql, MySql, Bootstrap, JQuery, ReactJs, Codelgniter, Docker, JavaScript.